export const questions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript ?",
        answers:[
            {text: "onSubmit()"},
            {text: "onLoad()"},
            {text: "isPostBack()"},
            {text: "onClick()"},
            {correct: "onClick()"}  
        ] 
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "min(x,y)"},
            {text: "Math.min(x,y)"},
            {text: "Math.min(xy)"},
            {text: "min(xy)"},
            {correct: "Math.min(x,y)"}  
        ]

    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "JavaScript is a ______ -side programming language.",
        answers: [
            {text: "Client"},
            {text: "Server"},
            {text: "Both"},
            {text: "None"},
            {correct: "Both"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which of the following will write the message 'Hello DataFlair!' in an alert box ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "alertBox(“Hello DataFlair!”)"},
            {text: "alert(Hello DataFlair!)"},
            {text: "msgAlert(“Hello DataFlair!”)"},
            {text: "alert(“Hello DataFlair!”)"},
            {correct: "alert(“Hello DataFlair!”)"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which are the correct “if” statements to execute certain code if “x” is equal to 2 ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "if(x 2)"},
            {text: "if(x = 2)"},
            {text: "if(x == 2)"},
            {text: "if(x != 2 )"},
            {correct: "if(x == 2)"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "JavaScript code can be called by using:",
        answers: [
            {text: "RMI"},
            {text: "Preprocessor"},
            {text: "Function / Method"},
            {text: "None of the above"},
            {correct: "Function / Method"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which is the correct JavaScript syntax to change the HTML content given below '\n' <p id=”test”>Hello World!</p>",
        answers: [
            {text: "document.getElementById(“test”).innerHTML = “Hello DataFlair!”"},
            {text: "document.getElementsById(“test”).innerHTML = “Hello DataFlair!”"},
            {text: "document.getElementById(test).innerHTML = “Hello DataFlair!”"},
            {text: "document.getElementByTagName(“p”)[0].innerHTML = “Hello DataFlair!”"},
            {correct: "document.getElementById(“test”).innerHTML = “Hello DataFlair!”"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Do you know what will be the output of this code?'\n' console.log(3 > 2 > 1).",
        answers: [
            {text: "true"},
            {text: "false"},
            {text: "NaN"},
            {text: "SyntaxError"},
            {correct: "false"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "JavaScript File Has An Extension of: ",
        answers: [
            {text: ".java"},
            {text: ".js"},
            {text: ".javascript"},
            {text: ".xml"},
            {correct: ".js"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which Of The Dialog Box Display a Message And a Data Entry Field?",
        answers: [
            {text: "alert()"},
            {text: "prompt()"},
            {text: "confirm()"},
            {text: "msg()"},
            {correct: "prompt()"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Javascript is a _____ language.",
        answers: [
            {text: "Programming"},
            {text: "Application"},
            {text: "None of the above"},
            {text: "Scripting"},
            {correct: "Scripting"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Which of the following purpose, JavaScript is designed for ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "To Execute Query Related to DB on Server"},
            {text: "To Style HTML Pages"},
            {text: "To Perform Server Side Scripting Opertion"},
            {text: "To add interactivity to HTML Pages."},
            {correct: "To add interactivity to HTML Pages."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "JavaScript can be written",
        answers: [
            {text: "directly on the Server Script"},
            {text: "directly into HTML pages"},
            {text: "All of the above"},
            {text: "None of the above"},
            {correct: "directly into HTML pages"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "Local Browser used for validations on the Web Pages uses:",
        answers: [
            {text: "Javascript"},
            {text: "Java"},
            {text: "HTML"},
            {text: "CSS"},
            {correct: "Javascript"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "JavaScript is a _____ Side Scripting Language.",
        answers: [
            {text: "Server"},
            {text: "Browser"},
            {text: "ISP"},
            {text: "None of the above"},
            {correct: "Browser"}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "Why JavaScript is called as Lightweight Programming Language ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "Because JS is client side scripting"},
            {text: "Because JS is available free of cost."},
            {text: "Because we can add programming functionality inside JS"},
            {text: "Because JS can provide programming functionality inside but up to certain extend."},
            {correct: "Because JS can provide programming functionality inside but up to certain extend."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "Which of the following is not javascript data types ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "Null type."},
            {text: "Undefined type."},
            {text: "Number type."},
            {text: "All of the above."},
            {correct: "All of the above."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: "What do you mean by the word 'JavaScript' ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "JavaScript is a scripting language used to make the website interactive."},
            {text: "JavaScript is an assembly language used to make the website interactive."},
            {text: "JavaScript is a compiled language used to make the website interactive."},
            {text: "None of the above."},
            {correct: "JavaScript is a scripting language used to make the website interactive."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: "Which is correct about JavaScript ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "JavaScript is an Object-Based language."},
            {text: "JavaScript is Assembly-language."},
            {text: "JavaScript is an Object-Oriented language."},
            {text: "JavaScript is a High-level language."},
            {correct: "JavaScript is an Object-Based language."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: "Which statement defines closures in JavaScript ? ",
        answers: [
            {text: "JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its inner function scope."},
            {text: "JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its lexical environment."},
            {text: "JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with the object to its inner function scope."},
            {text: "None of the above."},
            {correct: "JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its lexical environment."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: "Arrays in JavaScript are defined by which of the following statements ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "It is an ordered list of values."},
            {text: "It is an ordered list of objects."},
            {text: "It is an ordered list of string."},
            {text: "It is an ordered list of functions."},
            {correct: "It is an ordered list of values."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: "Which of the following is not an error in JavaScript ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "Missing of Bracket."},
            {text: "Division by zero."},
            {text: "Syntax error."},
            {text: "Missing of semicolons."},
            {correct: "Division by zero."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: "The main purpose of a 'Live Wire' in NetScape is to ________.",
        answers: [
            {text: "Create linkage between client side and server side."},
            {text: "Permit server side, JavaScript code, to connect to RDBMS."},
            {text: "Support only non relational database."},
            {text: "To interpret JavaScript code."},
            {correct: "Permit server side, JavaScript code, to connect to RDBMS."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: "The script tag must be placed in __________.",
        answers: [
            {text: "The head tag."},
            {text: "The head or body."},
            {text: "The title or head."},
            {text: "After the body tag."},
            {correct: "The head or body."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: "JavaScript is ideal to ________.",
        answers: [
            {text: "Make computations in HTML simpler."},
            {text: "Minimize storage requirements on the web server."},
            {text: "Increase the download time for the client."},
            {text: "Increase the loading time of the website."},
            {correct: "Minimize storage requirements on the web server."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        question: "What is the basic difference between JavaScript and Java ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "Functions are considered as fields."},
            {text: "Functions are values, and there is no hard distinction between methods and fields."},
            {text: "Variables are specific."},
            {text: "There is no difference."},
            {correct: "Functions are values, and there is no hard distinction between methods and fields."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        question: "Why JavaScript Engine is needed ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "Both Compiling & Interpreting the JavaScript."},
            {text: "Parsing the javascript."},
            {text: "Interpreting the JavaScript."},
            {text: "Compiling the JavaScript."},
            {correct: "Interpreting the JavaScript."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 27,
        question: "Which of the following methods/operation does javascript use instead of == and != ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "JavaScript uses equalto()."},
            {text: "JavaScript uses equals() and notequals() instead."},
            {text: "JavaScript uses bitwise checking."},
            {text: "JavaScript uses === and !== instead."},
            {correct: "JavaScript uses === and !== instead."}  
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 28,
        question: "What is the prototype represents in the following JavaScript code snippet ?",
        answers: [
            {text: "Not valid."},
            {text: "Prototype of a function."},
            {text: "Function javascript."},
            {text: "A custom constructor."},
            {correct: "A custom constructor."}  
        ]
    }
]

